Preliminary Guide to the Douglas M. Knight Records, 1949 - 1970
Duke University. University Archives
- Subject Files, 1952-1969
  - Committees (Box 6)
    - Administrative Changes [Very Informal], 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Administrative Council, 1964-1969, [2 folders] (Box 7)
    - Administrative Group, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
    - Admissions [Foreign Students], 1964-1967 (Box 7)
    - Aging and Human Development [Formerly Gerontology], 1963-1968 (Box 7)
    - Appeals Board, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Art, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Art Center Architect, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
    - Arts Council, 1965-1968 (Box 7)
    - Audio-Visual and Electronic Learning, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
    - Auditoriums [Educational Facilities Committee], 1964 (Box 7)
    - Biological Sciences Council [Genetics; Interdisciplinary Studies], 1963-1969 (Box 7)
    - Buildings and Grounds [Trustees], 1963-1969, 1963-1969, [3 folders] (Box 7)
    - Chapel Administration, 1963-1969 (Box 7)
    - Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Clinical Research on Human Subjects, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
    - Computer, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 7)
    - Courses of Instruction, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Curriculum, 1964-1969, [2 folders] (Box 7)
    - Dean of Trinity College Selection, 1963-1964 (Box 7)
    - Distinguished Professorships [William Heckscher], 1963-1966 (Box 7)
    - Educational Administration, 1963-1969 (Box 7)
    - Educational Facilities, 1962-1969, [4 folders] (Box 7)
    - Elections [University Faculty], 1964-1969 (Box 7)
    - Faculty Advisory Committee on Regional Educational Programs, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Faculty Committee for Student Concerns [Black Students], 1969 (Box 7)
    - Faculty Fringe Benefits, 1963-1965 (Box 7)
    - Faculty Hearing, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Faculty-Trustee Liaison, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
    - Fall-Out Preparedness, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Financial Aid, 1964-1968 (Box 7)
    - FM Radio Station, 1965-1968 (Box 7)
    - Forest [Fiber Industries Corp.], 1965-1969 (Box 7)
    - Forestry School Dean Search, 1966-1969 (Box 7)
    - Graduate Council [Executive Committee], 1963-1969 (Box 8)
    - Human Relations, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
    - Humanities Council, 1963-1969 (Box 8)
    - International Studies, 1963-1968 (Box 8)
    - Investment Committee [Duke University], 1964-1965 (Box 8)
    - Judicial Committee [Allen Building], 1968-1969 (Box 8)
    - Marine Laboratory Advisory, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Medical and Engineering, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
    - Medical Provost, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Mental Retardation and Human Development, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 8)
    - North Carolina College -- Duke, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Nursing Dean Recommendation, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
    - Nursing Education Study, 1965-1968 (Box 8)
    - Nursing School, 1963-1965 (Box 8)
    - Patent Policy (Box 8)
    - Physical Education Facilities, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Physical Sciences Council, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Pickets and Protests [Non-Academic Employees, Labor Relations], 1968 (Box 8)
    - Provost Search Committee, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Public Education and the Training of Teachers, 1963-1966 (Box 8)
    - Publications Board, 1963-1968 (Box 8)
    - Publicity, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Recreational Resources and Facilities, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Reorganization, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
    - Residential Life, 1967-1969, [2 folders] (Box 8)
    - Retirement, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Schedule, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
    - Science Development Program, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Search for President, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Size of the University, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
    - Social Science Council, 1964-1968 (Box 8)
    - Space Studies, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Special University Ceremonies, 1966-1968 (Box 8)
    - Student-Faculty-Administration [SFAC], 1963-1969, [4 folders] (Box 8)
    - Study Abroad, 1964-1968 (Box 8)
    - Summer Session, 1963 (Box 8)
    - Ten-Year Expansion Program [Trustee Committee], 1965 (Box 8)
    - Tenure Practices and Hearings, 1964-1969 (Box 8)
    - Trustee-Faculty and Trustee-Student Liaison, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Trustees' Committee for Institutional Advancement, 1964 (Box 8)
    - Undergraduate Faculty Council, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 8)
    - Undergraduate Instruction, 1967 (Box 8)
    - University Planning [Long-Range Planning], 1964 (Box 8)
    - University Planning Committee, 1963-1964, [3 folders] (Box 8)
    - University Planning Committee (Box 8)
      - Educational Goals Subcommittee, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
      - Graduate Affairs Subcommittee, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
    - University Policy and Planning Advisory Committee [UPPAC], 1963-1969, [5 folders] (Box 9)
    - Wade Committee, 1968 (Box 9)
    - West Campus Community Council, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Woman's College -- Search for a New Dean, 1968 (Box 9)
    - Year-Round Operations, 1965-1968 (Box 9)
  - Commonwealth Studies Center, 1962-1965 (Box 9)
  - Community Teaching Hospital [Cabarrus County], 1965-1968 (Box 9)
  - Computer Planning, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - Conference for Secondary School Counselors, 1964-1966 (Box 9)
  - Conference on Race Relations, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1966-1968 (Box 9)
  - Congressional Matters -- Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Congressmen (Box 9)
    - Ervin, Senator Sam J., Jr., 1965-1969 (Box 9)
    - Galifianakis, Rep. Nick, 1967-1969 (Box 9)
    - Galifianakis, Rep. Nick, 1967-1969 (Box 9)
    - Gardner, Rep. James C. [North Carolina Fund], 1967 (Box 9)
    - Jordan, Senator B. Everett, 1963-1969 (Box 9)
    - Kornegay, Rep. Horace, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - Continuing Education Institute [see also Gourman Report File], 1968 (Box 9)
  - Controversial Social Issues, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Convocation -- "Christianity and Social Revolution in Newly Developing Nations," 1964 (Box 9)
  - Convocation for New Students, 1963-1965 (Box 9)
  - Convocation to Open School Year, 1966-1969 (Box 9)
  - Cooperation -- UNC-Duke [Winchester Excavation], 1964-1968 (Box 9)
  - Cooperation with Developing Institutions in Region, 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - Cooperative Program in the Humanities, 1963-1969 (Box 9)
  - Cooperative Programs -- Miles College [Black College], 1966-1968 (Box 9)
  - Corbett, Horace, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
  - CORE, 1963-1964 (Box 9)
  - Corporate Board Memberships [University Presidents], 1968 (Box 9)
  - Corporate Gifts Advisory Committee -- William H. Rubbin, Chairman, 1965-1967 (Box 9)
  - Council of Southern Universities, 1963-1969, [3 folders] (Box 10)
  - Crank Letters, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 10)
  - Curriculum Planning -- Undergraduate, 1964-1968 (Box 10)
  - Dabney, Virginius [Public Relations], 1964 (Box 10)
  - Dad's Day, 1963-1968 (Box 10)
  - Daedalus Program, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 10)
  - Dante Celebration, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - Davison, Wilburt C. [Diary], 1964-1968 (Box 10)
  - Deans' Meetings, 1963-1968 (Box 10)
  - Demonstration [Vigil], April 1968, [2 folders] (Box 10)
  - Demonstration [Vigil] -- Letters, April 1968 (Box 10)
  - Denominational Centers, 1963-1964 (Box 10)
  - Development Office -- SACS Accreditation, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Distinguished Lectureships, 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminars, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - Divinity School, 1963-1969, [4 folders] (Box 10)
  - Divinity School (Box 10)
    - Altiser Affair, 1965-1966 (Box 10)
  - "Dixie," 1968 (Box 10)
  - Dow, Alden, 1964-1967 (Box 10)
  - Dozier, John M. [Building Program], 1963-1966 (Box 10)
  - Drinking [Alcohol Policy], 1964-1968 (Box 10)
  - Drugs, 1967-1968 (Box 10)
  - Duke, Doris, 1963-1969 (Box 10)
  - Duke, James B. Professorships, 1963-1965 (Box 10)
  - Duke Endowment (Box 10)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 10)
    - Allen, Joseph, 1963-1965 (Box 11)
    - Committee on Educational Institutions [Paul Clyde], 1963-1964, [2 folders] (Box 11)
    - Duke University Open Account, 1960-1965, [2 folders] (Box 11)
    - Hospital and Orphan Sections, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 11)
    - Perkins, Thomas L., 1963-1966 (Box 11)
    - Proposals, 1965-1968 (Box 11)
  - Duke Marine Laboratory, 1963-1968, [3 folders] (Box 11)
  - Duke Players, 1965-1967 (Box 11)
  - Duke Sailing Club, 1963-1965 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Counseling Center, 1964-1967 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Dining Halls, 1963-1968 (Box 11)
  - Duke University Editor, 1964-1968 (Box 11)
  - Durham Academy, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Durham Community Planning Council, 1963-1968 (Box 11)
  - Durham-Duke Group [Opportunity Up-Grading], 1967-1969 (Box 11)
  - Durham-Duke Program -- Annual Development - Fundraising, 1963-1968 (Box 11)
  - Eastward [Research vessel], 1964-1969, [2 folders] (Box 11)
  - Edgemont Community Center, 1967 (Box 11)
  - Education and World Affairs, [4 folders] (Box 11)
  - Education and World Affairs, 1962-1968, [3 folders] (Box 11)
  - Education Bills (Box 12)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 12)
    - Congress, 1965-1969 (Box 12)
  - Education Department, 1963-1965 (Box 12)
  - Education Improvement Program, 1964-1968 (Box 12)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 12)
  - Educational Policy -- Dr. Few, 1936; 1967 (Box 12)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1966-1967 (Box 12)
  - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships, 1968 (Box 12)
  - Eller, Aurelia, 1964-1969 (Box 12)
  - Engineering School, 1963-1967, [3 folders] (Box 12)
  - Erasmus Club, 1969 (Box 12)
  - Faculty and Staff -- Future, 1964-1969, [3 folders] (Box 12)
  - Faculty (Box 12)
    - Apartments, 1964 (Box 12)
    - Applications -- Grants, etc. [Procedure], 1966 (Box 12)
    - Club, 1961-1968 (Box 12)
    - Committee on Institutional Advancement, 1965-1966 (Box 12)
    - Handbook; Faculty Newsletter, 1963-1969 (Box 12)
    - Ideas, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
    - Liability Insurance Committee, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Meeting, 21 March 1968 (Box 12)
    - Needs, 1964 (Box 12)
    - Projections, 1966-1968 (Box 12)
    - Publications [Reprints have been removed], 1963 (Box 12)
    - Salaries, 1963-1965 (Box 12)
    - Salary Letters, 1964-1968 (Box 12)
    - Suggestions. Complaints, etc., 1964-1968 (Box 12)
  - Financial Aid, 1965-1969 (Box 12)
  - Flag Raising, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Flowers Memorial Collection, 1963 (Box 12)
  - Football, 1963-1965 (Box 12)
  - Foreign Service Institute [Duke-UNC-NCSU], 1966 (Box 12)
  - Foundations (Box 12)
    - Arts, Religion, and Culture (Foundation for), 1962-1967 (Box 12)
    - Ford (Box 12)
      - Cooperative Program in Teacher Education, 1963-1966 (Box 12)
      - Cooperative Program on Southern Teacher Education, 1965 (Box 12)
      - Duke-Emory-Vanderbilt-Tulane Grant, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
      - Economics Grants, 1963-1964 (Box 12)
      - General [Enrichment Program in Physics for Students from Black Colleges], 1964-1969, [2 folders] (Box 12)
      - Profile, 1963-1966, [2 folders] (Box 13)
    - Hartford, 1963-1965 (Box 13)
    - Hazen, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
    - Kenan, 1966-1969 (Box 13)
    - Mary Duke Biddle (Box 13)
    - Olin, 1963-1965 (Box 13)
    - Phillips [Academic Administration Internships], 1962-1966, [2 folders] (Box 13)
    - Proposals, 1963-1965, [3 folders] (Box 13)
    - Richardson, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Van Leer, 1964-1966, [8 folders] (Box 13)
    - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship, 1963-1968, [3 folders] (Box 13)
  - Founders' Day, 1962-1969, [2 folders] (Box 14)
  - Frank, W. O. -- Claim [Architect, Ofc. of Horace Trumbauer], 1944-1949; 1962-1967 (Box 14)
  - Fraternities (Box 14)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 14)
    - Title VI, 1965-1968 (Box 14)
  - Fulbright Program, 1963-1966 (Box 14)
  - Graduate Program in Business Administration, 1964-1969, [3 folders] (Box 14)
  - Graduate School, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 14)
  - Graduate School (Box 14)
    - Admissions, 1966-1968 (Box 14)
    - Dean Search, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
    - Tuition, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Griffith, William J., 1963-1965 (Box 14)
  - Gross Symposium re: Fifth Decade, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Guatemala, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
  - Guatemala and Puerto Rico, 1967-1969 (Box 14)
  - Hart, J. Deryl, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Health Planning Council, 1963-1965 (Box 14)
  - Heim, Peggy, 1965-1968 (Box 14)
  - Honors Program, 1963-1969 (Box 14)
  - Hopkins, Everett H., 1963-1966, [2 folders] (Box 14)
  - Housing (Box 14)
    - 1965-1969 (Box 14)
    - Damar Apartments [Married Student Housing], 1967-1968 (Box 14)
    - Sale of Married Student Housing, 1967, [2 folders] (Box 14)
  - Humanities and the Arts Symposium, Oct. 16-17, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Hunt, Joe, 1963-1968 (Box 15)
  - Iceland, 1964-1968 (Box 15)
  - Identification Cards, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Inaugural Planning Committee, 1963 (Box 15)
  - Institute -- African-American, 1963-1968 (Box 15)
  - Institute for Creative Studies, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1963-1969 (Box 15)
  - Institute of International Education, 1963-1969 (Box 15)
  - Institutional Advancement (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 15)
    - Field Representatives and others, 1968 (Box 15)
    - Fifth Decade Program, 1966-1969 (Box 15)
  - Institutional Studies Office, 1964, [2 folders] (Box 15)
  - Integration, 1963-1967 (Box 15)
  - Inter-Governmental Council [Student Government], 1965-1966 (Box 15)
  - International -- Alicia Patterson Fund, 1969 (Box 15)
  - International Association of Economics & Business Students, 1966 (Box 15)
  - International Consortium [Duke, Toronto, Sussex, East Africa], 1964-1966 (Box 15)
  - International Convocation "Pacem in Terris", 1965 (Box 15)
  - International Executive Service Corps, 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - International Foreign Studies, 1966-1968 1966-1968 (Box 15)
  - International Programs and Studies, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 15)
  - International Student Day, April 4, 1964 (Box 15)
  - International Students Advisory Committee, 1963 (Box 15)
  - International Students at Duke, 1963-1968 (Box 15)
  - Inter-University Committee on the Superior Student, 1964 (Box 15)
  - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants, 1963-1969 (Box 15)
  - "Introduction to the Humanities," 1967 (Box 15)
  - Investment Committee, 1964-1969, [3 folders] (Box 15)
  - Invitations Declined (Box 15)
    - General, 1964-1968, [2 folders] (Box 15)
    - Speaking, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 15)
  - Japan, 1965-1968 (Box 15)
  - John Price Jones Company, 1964-1965 (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Junior Science Symposium, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Kennedy Assassination -- University Policy, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Kennedy Library, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Knight, Douglas M. (Box 16)
    - American Express (Box 16)
    - Ashmore, Frank L., 1965 (Box 16)
    - Biographical material (Box 16)
    - City Club (Box 16)
    - Correspondence [with Daryl Hart & Chris Mimms prior to coming to Duke], 1962-1964 (Box 16)
    - Honorary Degrees [UNC, Carleton College], 1965-1966 (Box 16)
    - Hope Valley Country Club, 1963-1969 (Box 16)
    - Inauguration, 1963, [4 folders] (Box 16)
    - Itineraries, 1966-1969 (Box 16)
    - Leadership Conference, Nov. 1965 (Box 16)
    - Mailing Lists for Speeches, Etc. 1965-1969 (Box 16)
    - Material from Tokyo Meeting, 1965 (Box 16)
    - Memoranda, 1964-1969, [2 folders] (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966-1969 (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1964-1969 (Box 16)
    - Names and Addresses, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Newspaper Stories, etc., 1963 (Box 16)
    - Publications, 1967 (Box 16)
    - Resignation as President, 1969 (Box 16)
    - Rotary Club, 1963-1968 (Box 16)
    - Speeches, etc., 1963-1969 (Box 16)
    - Statements, 1963-1969 (Box 16)
    - ToBaC Club, 1963-1969 (Box 16)
    - Trustee Meeting [Fifth Decade], May 3, 1965 (Box 16)
    - Who's Who, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
  - Labor Relations, 1965-1969, [2 folders] (Box 16)
  - Law School, 1963-1968, [2 folders] (Box 16)
  - Law School (Box 16)
    - Admissions, 1968-1969 (Box 16)
    - Budget, 1963-1965 (Box 16)
    - Dean Search (Box 17)
      - 1965 (Box 17)
      - 1968 (Box 17)
    - Fund for Education in World Order, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
    - Grenville Clark Institute for World Law, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1963-1968 (Box 17)
    - Symposia, 1963-1968 (Box 17)
    - World Rule of Law Center, 1963-1968 (Box 17)
  - Learned Societies, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Leaves - Sabbaticals, etc., 1963-1965, [2 folders] (Box 17)
  - Lectureships [Dr. Ballantyne], 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Lee, Larry [Development], 1965-1969, see also Speeches, Loma and Alumni (Box 17)
  - Lewis, Harold W., 1963-1965 (Box 17)
  - Library (Box 17)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 17)
    - Committee on Administrative Systems, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Documentary Collections in Prospect [Papers of Famous Persons], 1965-1969 (Box 17)
    - Newman, Mrs. Ruth, 1966-1969 (Box 17)
    - Research Library for Arts & Sciences [Booklet], Feb. 1965 (Box 17)
    - Council, 1963-1969 (Box 17)
  - Long-Range Planning - Ideas, 1964-1966 (Box 17)
  - Major Speaker Invitations, 1967-1969 (Box 17)
  - Marine Corps, 1963 (Box 17)
  - Martin, Joseph B. [Assistant in the Office of the President], 1966-1969 (Box 17)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1966-1968 (Box 17)
  - Matheson, C. R. [Office of Business & Industrial Liason], 1964-1965 (Box 17)
  - Matthews, Maggie [Women Physicians in Training and Practice], 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - Medical Center (Box 17)
    - Allied Health Education, 1967 (Box 17)
    - Assistant Dean for Research, 1967 (Box 17)
    - "Biomagnetics" [W. C. Davison - Doris Duke Matter], 1965-1967 (Box 17)
    - Community Health Project, 1963 (Box 17)
    - Community Health Science, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
    - Development Program [Biomagnetic Research and Doris Duke], 1964-1967 (Box 17)
    - Federal Legislation, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Graduate Program in Hospital Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 17)
    - Hostel, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Hyperbaric Medicine and Conference [Nov. 1965], 1965-1968 (Box 17)
    - Inter-University Communications Council (EDUCOM), 1966-1968 (Box 17)
    - Inter-University Communications Council (INTERCOM), 1964-1969 (Box 18)
    - Inter-University Communications Council (INTRACOM), 1966-1967 (Box 18)
    - Long, E. Croft [International Work], 1965-1968 (Box 18)
    - "Man in the Sea" Program, 1966-1968 (Box 18)
    - MEDLARS Program [Medical Literature and Retrieval System], 1964-1967 (Box 18)
    - Mental Retardation Program, 1964-1965 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967, [2 folders] (Box 18)
    - Nursing Education Program -- Chowan College, 1964-1969 (Box 18)
    - Nursing School, 1966-1969 (Box 18)
    - Project MED-AID [Medical Assistance for Isolated Doctors], 1965 (Box 18)
    - Rehabilitation Research & Training Center, 1965 (Box 18)
    - Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 18)
    - School of Medicine -- New Curriculum, 1964 (Box 18)
    - Tuition and Financial Aid -- Medical School, 1968 (Box 18)
    - Woodhall, Barnes, 1965-1969 (Box 18)
    - Wrightsville Beach Laboratory [Marine Biomedical Research], 1965-1968 (Box 18)
    - Yearbook [The Aesculapian], 1964 (Box 18)
  - "Medicine in a Changing World" Symposium, Oct. 9-10, 1964 (Box 18)
  - Memorial Church Fund, Inc., 1964 (Box 18)
  - Methodist Church (Box 18)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 18)
    - Board of Education, 1963-1964 (Box 18)
    - Division of Higher Education [Latin American Program], 1965-1975 (Box 18)
  - Methodist Student Center, 1963-1964 (Box 18)
  - Modern Language Association, 1967-1969 (Box 18)
  - Moore, Gov. Dan K. [Nuclear Laboratory], 1963-1968 (Box 18)
  - Morocco (Box 18)
    - University of Tangier [International Affairs], 1966-1967 (Box 18)
    - Water Resources, 1966 (Box 18)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1963-1969 (Box 18)
  - National Aeronautics & Space Administration, 1963-1966, [3 folders] (Box 18)
  - National Catholic Conference on Interracial Justice, 1966-1969 (Box 18)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association [1.6 GPA Legislation], 1963-1969 (Box 18)
  - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 18)
    - 1963-1969 (Box 18)
    - "A Study of the Influence on Higher Ed. of Accreditation in Teacher Ed," 1963-1968 (Box 18)
    - NCATE, 1963-1968, [3 folders] (Box 19)
  - National Council for Civic Responsibilities [Arthur Larson], 1964-1965 (Box 19)
  - National Defense Education Act, 1963-1967 (Box 19)
  - National Defense Student Loan Program, 1965 (Box 19)
  - National Environmental Health Sciences Center, 1965-1966 (Box 19)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1963 (Box 19)
  - National League for Nursing [Accreditation], 1964-1967 (Box 19)
  - National Merit Scholarship Corp., 1963-1969, [3 folders] (Box 19)
  - National Science Foundation, 1963-1970, [5 folders] (Box 19)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 19)
    - Advisory Comm. for Institutional Relations, 1965-1968, [2 folders] (Box 19)
    - Computing Services Grant, April, 1968 (Box 19)
    - Divisional Committee for Institutional Programs, 1964-1965, [2 folders] (Box 19)
    - Institutional Grants, 1964-1969 (Box 19)
    - Science Development Program, 1964-1969, [2 folders] (Box 20)
  - National Sponsoring Committee [Fifth Decade Program] James R. Killian, Jr. Chairman, 1965-1969 (Box 20)
  - Naval ROTC [Air Force ROTC], 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 20)
  - Negro Sit-In, 1967 -- Letters Answered (Box 20)
  - Newcomen Society, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
  - Nixon, Richard Milhous [Nixon Portrait], 1965-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina, Learning Institute of [LINC], 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 20)
  - North Carolina -- University, 1964-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Academy of Sciences, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Advancement School, 1963-1967 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Appalachian Center, 1964 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Association of Colleges & Universities [Formerly N. C. College Conference], 1963-1968 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Associations -- General, 1964 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Board of Science & Technology [Nuclear Laboratory Proposal], 1964-1967 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Central University [North Carolina College], 1963-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Commission on Higher Education Facilities, 1964-1968, [2 folders] (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Department of Public Instruction, 1964-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Economic Opportunity Program [Operation Breakthrough], 1966 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Folklore Society, 1963 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Fund -- Operation Breakthrough, 1963-1968 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Legislative Commission to Study Library Support in the State (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Museum of Art, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Press Association, 1963-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina School of the Arts, 1964-1967 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Society of New York, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina State Board of Higher Education [Physical Plant Evaluation 1930-1960], 1963-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina State Highway Commission [Joe Hunt, 751], 1965-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina State Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina State University -- Raleigh, 1965-1969 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Symphony, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1966-1967 (Box 20)
  - Nursing School, 1963-1966 (Box 20)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1963-1969, [2 folders] (Box 20)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1963-1969 (Box 21)
  - Operations Research Committee, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Oral History Project, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Organ -- Indoor Stadium [Proposed Gift from Centre Theater], 1966 (Box 21)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - Orientation Week, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - Parking Facilities, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Peace Corps, 1964-1969 (Box 21)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1963-1969 (Box 21)
  - Phytotron, 1963-1969 (Box 21)
  - Pianos, 1966 (Box 21)
  - "Pickets and Protest" Policy, 1967-1968, [3 folders] (Box 21)
  - Piracy [Duke and UNC No-raiding Agreement], 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Polanyi, Michael, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - Porter Book [Trinity and Duke], 1964-1968 (Box 21)
  - Presidency, University -- Survey of Activities [Time Study], 1968 (Box 21)
  - President -- Reports to the, 1963-1964; 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - President's Address to Trustees, 1963 (Box 21)